**PRIVACY NOTICE AND TERMS OF SERVICE**

**Last updated April 18, 2024**

Thank you for choosing to be part of our community at CWBCHICAGO LLC (“**Company**“, “**we**“, “**us**“, “**our**“). We are committed to protecting your personal information and your right to privacy. If you have any questions or concerns about this privacy notice, or our practices with regards to your personal information, please contact us at privacy@cwbchicago.com.

When you visit our website CWBCHICAGO.COM (the “**Website**“), and more generally, use any of our services (the “**Services**“, which include the Website), we appreciate that you are trusting us with your personal information. We take your privacy very seriously. In this privacy notice, we seek to explain to you in the clearest way possible what information we collect, how we use it and what rights you have in relation to it. We hope you take some time to read through it carefully, as it is important. If there are any terms in this privacy notice that you do not agree with, please discontinue use of our Services immediately.

This privacy notice applies to all information collected through our Services (which, as described above, includes our Website), as well as, any related services, sales, marketing or events.

**Please read this privacy notice carefully as it will help you understand what we do with the information that we collect.**

**1\. WHAT INFORMATION DO WE COLLECT?**

**Personal information you disclose to us**

**_In Short:_**  _We collect personal information that you provide to us._

We collect personal information that you voluntarily provide to us when you register on the Website, express an interest in obtaining information about us or our products and Services, when you participate in activities on the Website or otherwise when you contact us.

The personal information that we collect depends on the context of your interactions with us and the Website, the choices you make and the products and features you use. The personal information we collect may include the following:

**Personal Information Provided by You.** We collect names; phone numbers; email addresses; mailing addresses; billing addresses; debit/credit card numbers; contact or authentication data; and other similar information.

**Payment Data.** We may collect data necessary to process your payment if you make purchases, such as your payment instrument number (such as a credit card number), and the security code associated with your payment instrument. All payment data is stored by PayPal.com. You may find their privacy notice link(s) here: [https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full](https://www.paypal.com/us/webapps/mpp/ua/privacy-full).

All personal information that you provide to us must be true, complete and accurate, and you must notify us of any changes to such personal information.

**Information automatically collected**

**_In Short:_**  _Some information — such as your Internet Protocol (IP) address and/or browser and device characteristics — is collected automatically when you visit our Website._

We automatically collect certain information when you visit, use or navigate the Website. This information does not reveal your specific identity (like your name or contact information) but may include device and usage information, such as your IP address, browser and device characteristics, operating system, language preferences, referring URLs, device name, country, location, information about how and when you use our Website and other technical information. This information is primarily needed to maintain the security and operation of our Website, and for our internal analytics and reporting purposes.

Like many businesses, we also collect information through cookies and similar technologies.

The information we collect includes:

* _Log and Usage Data._ Log and usage data is service-related, diagnostic, usage and performance information our servers automatically collect when you access or use our Website and which we record in log files. Depending on how you interact with us, this log data may include your IP address, device information, browser type and settings and information about your activity in the Website (such as the date/time stamps associated with your usage, pages and files viewed, searches and other actions you take such as which features you use), device event information (such as system activity, error reports (sometimes called ‘crash dumps’) and hardware settings).

* _Device Data._ We collect device data such as information about your computer, phone, tablet or other device you use to access the Website. Depending on the device used, this device data may include information such as your IP address (or proxy server), device and application identification numbers, location, browser type, hardware model Internet service provider and/or mobile carrier, operating system and system configuration information.

**Information collected from other sources**

**_In Short:_**  _We may collect limited data from public databases, marketing partners, and other outside sources._

In order to enhance our ability to provide relevant marketing, offers and services to you and update our records, we may obtain information about you from other sources, such as public databases, joint marketing partners, affiliate programs, data providers, as well as from other third parties. This information includes mailing addresses, job titles, email addresses, phone numbers, intent data (or user behavior data), Internet Protocol (IP) addresses, social media profiles, social media URLs and custom profiles, for purposes of targeted advertising and event promotion.

**2\. HOW DO WE USE YOUR INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_**  _We process your information for purposes based on legitimate business interests, the fulfillment of our contract with you, compliance with our legal obligations, and/or your consent._

We use personal information collected via our Website for a variety of business purposes described below. We process your personal information for these purposes in reliance on our legitimate business interests, in order to enter into or perform a contract with you, with your consent, and/or for compliance with our legal obligations. We indicate the specific processing grounds we rely on next to each purpose listed below.

We use the information we collect or receive:

* **To facilitate account creation and logon process.** If you choose to link your account with us to a third-party account (such as your Google or Facebook account), we use the information you allowed us to collect from those third parties to facilitate account creation and logon process for the performance of the contract.

* **To post testimonials.** We post testimonials on our Website that may contain personal information. Prior to posting a testimonial, we will obtain your consent to use your name and the content of the testimonial. If you wish to update, or delete your testimonial, please contact us at privacy@cwbchicago.com and be sure to include your name, testimonial location, and contact information.

* **Request feedback.** We may use your information to request feedback and to contact you about your use of our Website.

* **To enable user-to-user communications.** We may use your information in order to enable user-to-user communications with each user’s consent.

* **To manage user accounts.** We may use your information for the purposes of managing our account and keeping it in working order.

* **To send administrative information to you.** We may use your personal information to send you product, service and new feature information and/or information about changes to our terms, conditions, and policies.

* **To protect our Services.** We may use your information as part of our efforts to keep our Website safe and secure (for example, for fraud monitoring and prevention).

* **To enforce our terms, conditions and policies for business purposes, to comply with legal and regulatory requirements or in connection with our contract.**

* **To respond to legal requests and prevent harm.** If we receive a subpoena or other legal request, we may need to inspect the data we hold to determine how to respond.

* **Fulfill and manage your orders.** We may use your information to fulfill and manage your orders, payments, returns, and exchanges made through the Website.

* **Administer prize draws and competitions.** We may use your information to administer prize draws and competitions when you elect to participate in our competitions.

* **To deliver and facilitate delivery of services to the user.** We may use your information to provide you with the requested service.

* **To respond to user inquiries/offer support to users.** We may use your information to respond to your inquiries and solve any potential issues you might have with the use of our Services.

* **To send you marketing and promotional communications.** We and/or our third-party marketing partners may use the personal information you send to us for our marketing purposes, if this is in accordance with your marketing preferences. For example, when expressing an interest in obtaining information about us or our Website, subscribing to marketing or otherwise contacting us, we will collect personal information from you. You can opt-out of our marketing emails at any time (see the “[WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS](https://cwbchicago.com/26359-2#privacyrights)” below).

* **Deliver targeted advertising to you.** We may use your information to develop and display personalized content and advertising (and work with third parties who do so) tailored to your interests and/or location and to measure its effectiveness.

* **For other business purposes.** We may use your information for other business purposes, such as data analysis, identifying usage trends, determining the effectiveness of our promotional campaigns and to evaluate and improve our Website, products, marketing and your experience. We may use and store this information in aggregated and anonymized form so that it is not associated with individual end users and does not include personal information. We will not use identifiable personal information without your consent.

**3\. WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?**

**_In Short:_**  _We only share information with your consent, to comply with laws, to provide you with services, to protect your rights, or to fulfill business obligations._

We may process or share your data that we hold based on the following legal basis:

* **Consent:** We may process your data if you have given us specific consent to use your personal information for a specific purpose.

* **Legitimate Interests:** We may process your data when it is reasonably necessary to achieve our legitimate business interests.

* **Performance of a Contract:** Where we have entered into a contract with you, we may process your personal information to fulfill the terms of our contract.

* **Legal Obligations:** We may disclose your information where we are legally required to do so in order to comply with applicable law, governmental requests, a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process, such as in response to a court order or a subpoena (including in response to public authorities to meet national security or law enforcement requirements).

* **Vital Interests:** We may disclose your information where we believe it is necessary to investigate, prevent, or take action regarding potential violations of our policies, suspected fraud, situations involving potential threats to the safety of any person and illegal activities, or as evidence in litigation in which we are involved.

More specifically, we may need to process your data or share your personal information in the following situations:

* **Business Transfers.** We may share or transfer your information in connection with, or during negotiations of, any merger, sale of company assets, financing, or acquisition of all or a portion of our business to another company.

* **Vendors, Consultants and Other Third-Party Service Providers.** We may share your data with third-party vendors, service providers, contractors or agents who perform services for us or on our behalf and require access to such information to do that work. Examples include: payment processing, data analysis, email delivery, hosting services, customer service and marketing efforts. We may allow selected third parties to use tracking technology on the Website, which will enable them to collect data on our behalf about how you interact with our Website over time. This information may be used to, among other things, analyze and track data, determine the popularity of certain content, pages or features, and better understand online activity. Unless described in this notice, we do not share, sell, rent or trade any of your information with third parties for their promotional purposes. We have contracts in place with our data processors, which are designed to help safeguard your personal information. This means that they cannot do anything with your personal information unless we have instructed them to do it. They will also not share your personal information with any organization apart from us. They also commit to protect the data they hold on our behalf and to retain it for the period we instruct.

* **Affiliates.** We may share your information with our affiliates, in which case we will require those affiliates to honor this privacy notice. Affiliates include our parent company and any subsidiaries, joint venture partners or other companies that we control or that are under common control with us.

* **Business Partners.** We may share your information with our business partners to offer you certain products, services or promotions.

**4\. WHO WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH?**     

**_In Short:_**  _We only share information with the following third parties._

We only share and disclose your information with the following third parties. We have categorized each party so that you may be easily understand the purpose of our data collection and processing practices. If we have processed your data based on your consent and you wish to revoke your consent, please contact us using the contact details provided in the section below titled “[HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?](https://cwbchicago.com/26359-2#contact)“.

* **Advertising, Direct Marketing, and Lead Generation**

This Site is affiliated with CMI Marketing, Inc., d/b/a Raptive (“Raptive”) for the purposes of placing advertising on the Site, and Raptive will collect and use certain data for advertising purposes. To learn more about Raptive’s data usage, click here: [https://raptive.com/creator-advertising-privacy-statement](https://raptive.com/creator-advertising-privacy-statement)

We use Google Analytics to analyze the use of our website. Google Analytics gathers information about website use by means of cookies. The information gathered relating to our website is used to create reports about the use of our website. Google’s privacy policy is available at: [https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/](https://www.google.com/policies/privacy/)

**5\. DO WE USE COOKIES AND OTHER TRACKING TECHNOLOGIES?**

**_In Short:_**  _We may use cookies and other tracking technologies to collect and store your information._

We may use cookies and similar tracking technologies (like web beacons and pixels) to access or store information. Specific information about how we use such technologies and how you can refuse certain cookies is set out in our Cookie Notice.

**6\. IS YOUR INFORMATION TRANSFERRED INTERNATIONALLY?**     

**_In Short:_**  _We may transfer, store, and process your information in countries other than your own._

Our servers are located in United States. If you are accessing our Website from outside United States, please be aware that your information may be transferred to, stored, and processed by us in our facilities and by those third parties with whom we may share your personal information (see “[WILL YOUR INFORMATION BE SHARED WITH ANYONE?](https://cwbchicago.com/26359-2#infoshare)” above), in and other countries.

If you are a resident in the European Economic Area, then these countries may not necessarily have data protection laws or other similar laws as comprehensive as those in your country. We will however take all necessary measures to protect your personal information in accordance with this privacy notice and applicable law.

European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses:

We have implemented measures to protect your personal information, including by using the European Commission’s Standard Contractual Clauses for transfers of personal information between our group companies and between us and our third-party providers. These clauses require all recipients to protect all personal information that they process originating from the EEA in accordance with European data protection laws and regulations. Our Standard Contractual Clauses can be provided upon request. We have implemented similar appropriate safeguards with our third-party service providers and partners and further details can be provided upon request.

**7\. WHAT IS OUR STANCE ON THIRD-PARTY WEBSITES?**

**_In Short:_**  _We are not responsible for the safety of any information that you share with third-party providers who advertise, but are not affiliated with, our Website._

The Website may contain advertisements from third parties that are not affiliated with us and which may link to other websites, online services or mobile applications. We cannot guarantee the safety and privacy of data you provide to any third parties. Any data collected by third parties is not covered by this privacy notice. We are not responsible for the content or privacy and security practices and policies of any third parties, including other websites, services or applications that may be linked to or from the Website. You should review the policies of such third parties and contact them directly to respond to your questions.

**8\. HOW LONG DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION?**

**_In Short:_**  _We keep your information for as long as necessary to fulfill the purposes outlined in this privacy notice unless otherwise required by law._

We will only keep your personal information for as long as it is necessary for the purposes set out in this privacy notice, unless a longer retention period is required or permitted by law (such as tax, accounting or other legal requirements). No purpose in this notice will require us keeping your personal information for longer than sixty (60) months past the termination of the user’s account.

When we have no ongoing legitimate business need to process your personal information, we will either delete or anonymize such information, or, if this is not possible (for example, because your personal information has been stored in backup archives), then we will securely store your personal information and isolate it from any further processing until deletion is possible.

**9\. HOW DO WE KEEP YOUR INFORMATION SAFE?**

**_In Short:_**  _We aim to protect your personal information through a system of organizational and technical security measures._

We have implemented appropriate technical and organizational security measures designed to protect the security of any personal information we process. However, despite our safeguards and efforts to secure your information, no electronic transmission over the Internet or information storage technology can be guaranteed to be 100% secure, so we cannot promise or guarantee that hackers, cybercriminals, or other unauthorized third parties will not be able to defeat our security, and improperly collect, access, steal, or modify your information. Although we will do our best to protect your personal information, transmission of personal information to and from our Website is at your own risk. You should only access the Website within a secure environment.

**10\. DO WE COLLECT INFORMATION FROM MINORS?**

**_In Short:_**  _We do not knowingly collect data from or market to children under 18 years of age._

We do not knowingly solicit data from or market to children under 18 years of age. By using the Website, you represent that you are at least 18 or that you are the parent or guardian of such a minor and consent to such minor dependent’s use of the Website. If we learn that personal information from users less than 18 years of age has been collected, we will deactivate the account and take reasonable measures to promptly delete such data from our records. If you become aware of any data we may have collected from children under age 18, please contact us at privacy@cwbchicago.com.

**11\. WHAT ARE YOUR PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

**_In Short:_**  _In some regions, such as the European Economic Area, you have rights that allow you greater access to and control over your personal information. You may review, change, or terminate your account at any time._

In some regions (like the European Economic Area), you have certain rights under applicable data protection laws. These may include the right (i) to request access and obtain a copy of your personal information, (ii) to request rectification or erasure; (iii) to restrict the processing of your personal information; and (iv) if applicable, to data portability. In certain circumstances, you may also have the right to object to the processing of your personal information. To make such a request, please use the [contact details](https://cwbchicago.com/26359-2#contact) provided below. We will consider and act upon any request in accordance with applicable data protection laws.

If we are relying on your consent to process your personal information, you have the right to withdraw your consent at any time. Please note however that this will not affect the lawfulness of the processing before its withdrawal, nor will it affect the processing of your personal information conducted in reliance on lawful processing grounds other than consent.

If you are a resident in the European Economic Area and you believe we are unlawfully processing your personal information, you also have the right to complain to your local data protection supervisory authority. You can find their contact details here: [http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index\_en.htm](http://ec.europa.eu/justice/data-protection/bodies/authorities/index_en.htm).

If you are a resident in Switzerland, the contact details for the data protection authorities are available here: [https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home.html](https://www.edoeb.admin.ch/edoeb/en/home.html).

If you have questions or comments about your privacy rights, you may email us at privacy@cwbchicago.com.

**Account Information**

If you would at any time like to review or change the information in your account or terminate your account, you can:

* Contact us using the contact information provided.

Upon your request to terminate your account, we will deactivate or delete your account and information from our active databases. However, we may retain some information in our files to prevent fraud, troubleshoot problems, assist with any investigations, enforce our Terms of Use and/or comply with applicable legal requirements.

**Cookies and similar technologies:** Most Web browsers are set to accept cookies by default. If you prefer, you can usually choose to set your browser to remove cookies and to reject cookies. If you choose to remove cookies or reject cookies, this could affect certain features or services of our Website. To opt-out of interest-based advertising by advertisers on our Website visit [http://www.aboutads.info/choices/](http://www.aboutads.info/choices/).

**Opting out of email marketing:** You can unsubscribe from our marketing email list at any time by clicking on the unsubscribe link in the emails that we send or by contacting us using the details provided below. You will then be removed from the marketing email list — however, we may still communicate with you, for example to send you service-related emails that are necessary for the administration and use of your account, to respond to service requests, or for other non-marketing purposes. To otherwise opt-out, you may:

* Contact us using the contact information provided.

**12\. CONTROLS FOR DO-NOT-TRACK FEATURES**

Most web browsers and some mobile operating systems and mobile applications include a Do-Not-Track (“DNT”) feature or setting you can activate to signal your privacy preference not to have data about your online browsing activities monitored and collected. At this stage no uniform technology standard for recognizing and implementing DNT signals has been finalized. As such, we do not currently respond to DNT browser signals or any other mechanism that automatically communicates your choice not to be tracked online. If a standard for online tracking is adopted that we must follow in the future, we will inform you about that practice in a revised version of this privacy notice. 

**13\. DO CALIFORNIA RESIDENTS HAVE SPECIFIC PRIVACY RIGHTS?**

**_In Short:_**  _Yes, if you are a resident of California, you are granted specific rights regarding access to your personal information._

California Civil Code Section 1798.83, also known as the “Shine The Light” law, permits our users who are California residents to request and obtain from us, once a year and free of charge, information about categories of personal information (if any) we disclosed to third parties for direct marketing purposes and the names and addresses of all third parties with which we shared personal information in the immediately preceding calendar year. If you are a California resident and would like to make such a request, please submit your request in writing to us using the contact information provided below.

If you are under 18 years of age, reside in California, and have a registered account with the Website, you have the right to request removal of unwanted data that you publicly post on the Website. To request removal of such data, please contact us using the contact information provided below, and include the email address associated with your account and a statement that you reside in California. We will make sure the data is not publicly displayed on the Website, but please be aware that the data may not be completely or comprehensively removed from all our systems (e.g. backups, etc.).

**14\. DO WE MAKE UPDATES TO THIS NOTICE?**     

_**In Short:**  Yes, we will update this notice as necessary to stay compliant with relevant laws._

We may update this privacy notice from time to time. The updated version will be indicated by an updated “Revised” date and the updated version will be effective as soon as it is accessible. If we make material changes to this privacy notice, we may notify you either by prominently posting a notice of such changes or by directly sending you a notification. We encourage you to review this privacy notice frequently to be informed of how we are protecting your information.

**15\. HOW CAN YOU CONTACT US ABOUT THIS NOTICE?**     

If you have questions or comments about this notice, you may email us at privacy@cwbchicago.com or by mail to:

CWBCHICAGO LLC  
111 North Wabash Ave. Ste.100  
The Garland Building #3466  
Chicago, IL 60602

**16\. HOW CAN YOU REVIEW, UPDATE, OR DELETE THE DATA WE COLLECT FROM YOU?**     

Based on the applicable laws of your country, you may have the right to request access to the personal information we collect from you, change that information, or delete it in some circumstances. To request to review, update, or delete your personal information, please visit: privacy@cwbchicago.com. We will respond to your request within 30 days.

**16\. WHAT IS YOUR ARTIFICIAL INTELLIGENCE POLICY?**     

The owner of this website does not consent to the content on this website being used or downloaded by any third parties for the purposes of developing, training or operating artificial intelligence or other machine learning systems (“Artificial Intelligence Purposes”), except as authorized by the owner in writing (including written electronic communication). Absent such consent, users of this website, including any third parties accessing the website through automated systems, are prohibited from using any of the content on the website for Artificial Intelligence Purposes. Users or automated systems that fail to respect these choices will be considered to have breached these TERMS OF SERVICE.

We have included on the pages of this website a robots meta tag with the “noai” or “noimageai” directive in the head section of the HTML page. Please note that even if such directives are not present on any web page or content file, this website still does not grant consent to use any content for Artificial Intelligence Purposes unless such consent is expressly contained.

This privacy policy was created in party by using [Termly’s Privacy Policy Generator](https://termly.io/products/privacy-policy-generator/?ftseo).

Austin

### [McDonald’s patrons tackled and beat an armed robber until cops arrived, Chicago police report says](https://cwbchicago.com/2024/12/mcdonalds-patrons-tackled-and-beat-an-armed-robber-until-cops-arrived-chicago-police-report-says.html "McDonald’s patrons tackled and beat an armed robber until cops arrived, Chicago police report says")

A man who robbed a McDonald’s customer at gunpoint on the West Side was hospitalized after the restaurant’s patrons ganged up on him and beat him until Chicago police arrived, officials said. And, prosecutors claim, it was the second time in ten days that the gunman had robbed the same victim inside the same restaurant.[](https://cwbchicago.com/2024/12/mcdonalds-patrons-tackled-and-beat-an-armed-robber-until-cops-arrived-chicago-police-report-says.html "McDonald’s patrons tackled and beat an armed robber until cops arrived, Chicago police report says")

CTA

### [Woman was part of five-person mob that mugged Red Line passengers, prosecutors claim](https://cwbchicago.com/2024/12/woman-was-part-of-five-person-mob-that-mugged-red-line-passengers-prosecutors-claim.html "Woman was part of five-person mob that mugged Red Line passengers, prosecutors claim")

Prosecutors say a woman on felony pretrial release was part of a five-person mob that attacked and robbed two men in separate crimes on the Red Line in October.[](https://cwbchicago.com/2024/12/woman-was-part-of-five-person-mob-that-mugged-red-line-passengers-prosecutors-claim.html "Woman was part of five-person mob that mugged Red Line passengers, prosecutors claim")

West Town

### [10+ years in federal prison for man who carjacked couple because he needed to get home quickly](https://cwbchicago.com/2024/12/10-years-in-federal-prison-for-man-who-carjacked-couple-because-he-needed-to-get-home-quickly.html "10+ years in federal prison for man who carjacked couple because he needed to get home quickly")

The decision to carjack a couple at gunpoint because the driver of his car was going too slow and he wanted to get home has landed a Chicago man in federal prison. Naronn Cain, 27, received a sentence of 10 years and 5 months from U.S. District Judge John Blakey upon pleading guilty to carjacking and using a firearm during the commission of a violent crime.[](https://cwbchicago.com/2024/12/10-years-in-federal-prison-for-man-who-carjacked-couple-because-he-needed-to-get-home-quickly.html "10+ years in federal prison for man who carjacked couple because he needed to get home quickly")

#### Daily email newsletter

Sign up to receive a daily summary of CWBChicago's latest stories.

Subscribe

Loading...

#### Thank you!

You have successfully joined our subscriber list.

#### Follow Us

Search

Search

###### Become A Subscriber

Our work is only possible because readers like you have chosen to invest in our efforts.

CWBChicago has no corporate sponsors and no backing by foundations or political groups.

You will receive exclusive reports and member-only services throughout the year.

Your subscription will help offset reporting expenses and allow us to provide deeper, more meaningful coverage year-round.

Thank you.

###### Neighborhood News

###### About CWBChicago

CWBChicago was created in 2013 by five Chicagoans who had grown disheartened with inaccurate information that was being provided at local Community Policing (CAPS) meetings.

Our coverage area has expanded to cover other North Side neighborhoods. But our mission remains unchanged: To provide original public safety reporting with better context and greater detail than mainstream media outlets.

###### Other Places of Interest

Civil court filings and decisions

Daily news roundup by Charlie Meyerson

CPD and CFD reference sites

Independently compiled homicide and crime statistics for Chicago

Blog covering the Cook County Courts and judges

**Sarcasm and silliness from a Windy City cop

Neighborhood news and activities

Long-running neighborhood blog

© 2024 CWBChicago LLC. All rights reserved.
